[{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678839004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":32772,"timeElapsed":53034},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678846251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":7243,"timeElapsed":60281},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678850605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":4352,"timeElapsed":64636},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678854383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":3775,"timeElapsed":68414},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678867220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":12834,"timeElapsed":81250},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678871386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4163,"timeElapsed":85416},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678878343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":6955,"timeElapsed":92374},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678887099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":8752,"timeElapsed":101129},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678928266,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":41164,"timeElapsed":142296},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678936744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7274,"timeElapsed":150775},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678940532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3785,"timeElapsed":154562},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678952122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":11587,"timeElapsed":166152},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678955178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3055,"timeElapsed":169209},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678960170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":4989,"timeElapsed":174201},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678962194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2022,"timeElapsed":176225},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678967518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":5320,"timeElapsed":181548},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678972108,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4589,"timeElapsed":186139},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678979750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":7639,"timeElapsed":193781},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678990290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":9431,"timeElapsed":204320},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678995091,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4800,"timeElapsed":209122},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679040769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":45676,"timeElapsed":254800},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679044964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4193,"timeElapsed":258995},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679048254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3287,"timeElapsed":262285},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679054929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":6673,"timeElapsed":268960},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679092376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":37445,"timeElapsed":306407},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679096091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3713,"timeElapsed":310121},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679100326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4233,"timeElapsed":314356},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679103871,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3543,"timeElapsed":317902},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679196004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":90799,"timeElapsed":410035},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679220040,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":24032,"timeElapsed":434070},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679229191,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":9148,"timeElapsed":443222},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679231837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2643,"timeElapsed":445868},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679265553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":33713,"timeElapsed":479584},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679268801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3246,"timeElapsed":482832},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679272131,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3328,"timeElapsed":486162},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679275476,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3342,"timeElapsed":489506},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679278003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2525,"timeElapsed":492033},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679286212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":7286,"timeElapsed":500243},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679288917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2702,"timeElapsed":502948},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679294372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5453,"timeElapsed":508402},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679297069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2695,"timeElapsed":511099},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679300726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3656,"timeElapsed":514757},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679303164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2437,"timeElapsed":517195},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679305531,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2364,"timeElapsed":519562},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679308115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2582,"timeElapsed":522146},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679314940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6823,"timeElapsed":528971},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679321485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":5637,"timeElapsed":535516},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679323374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1887,"timeElapsed":537404},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679325941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2566,"timeElapsed":539972},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679328124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2181,"timeElapsed":542155},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679330761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2635,"timeElapsed":544792},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679333346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2584,"timeElapsed":547377},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679336730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3382,"timeElapsed":550761},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679338983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2250,"timeElapsed":553014},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679342160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3174,"timeElapsed":556191},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679395116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":51590,"timeElapsed":609147},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679397804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2683,"timeElapsed":611834},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679416233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":18427,"timeElapsed":630264},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679418496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2259,"timeElapsed":632526},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679420958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2460,"timeElapsed":634989},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679423421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2460,"timeElapsed":637452},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679426254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2830,"timeElapsed":640284},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679428315,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2059,"timeElapsed":642346},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679430875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2557,"timeElapsed":644905},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679586402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":154515,"timeElapsed":800433},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679588842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2438,"timeElapsed":802873},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679592172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3327,"timeElapsed":806203},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679594329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2155,"timeElapsed":808360},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679599849,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5517,"timeElapsed":813880},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679604463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4612,"timeElapsed":818494},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679608217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3751,"timeElapsed":822248},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679611009,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2790,"timeElapsed":825039},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679617146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6135,"timeElapsed":831177},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679619290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2140,"timeElapsed":833321},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679641735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":19318,"timeElapsed":855766},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679644854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3117,"timeElapsed":858885},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679647832,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2976,"timeElapsed":861863},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679650325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2491,"timeElapsed":864356},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679653462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3134,"timeElapsed":867493},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679655675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2210,"timeElapsed":869706},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679686053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":30375,"timeElapsed":900083},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679688467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2412,"timeElapsed":902498},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679691290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2821,"timeElapsed":905321},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679698267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6094,"timeElapsed":912298},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679701099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2829,"timeElapsed":915130},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679703555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2454,"timeElapsed":917586},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679705566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2009,"timeElapsed":919597},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679707790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2221,"timeElapsed":921821},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679710044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2252,"timeElapsed":924075},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679712802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2756,"timeElapsed":926833},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679715096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2292,"timeElapsed":929127},{"subjectID":"7zm3tmragd","prolificID":"65a68c22822003df4f097af2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b38b4f02306d96243d8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679717221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2123,"timeElapsed":931252}]